And it's the end of the world, cool, my friend.
They just pay you to hold the camera, or also to talk?
I've been above, I've been above, so they pay one and they get two, exactly.
I'm, I'm paying, so yeah.
This is your guy, not the Norwegian.
This is your YouTube.
Ah, we're gonna get you more followers now.
Don't worry, so we can talk a lot
of most fantastic trackers who knows how to score goals.
I'll be honest with you, do you think people underrate you sometimes?
Just think you can just score in the box?
Underrate me?
No, but the expectations are so high.
I scored, how many goals did I score in Premier League this season?
27?
It wasn't expected, yeah.
If I score under 30, it's a decent season.
If I score under 25, it's a bad season.
Last year, I think I scored 21 or 22, and that was a bad season.
Which is good.
That's good.
Miami, first impressions?
Humid, beautiful, good weather, good food, good hotel, nice people.
Just tell us how you've been recovering from the last match.
Resting?
Yeah, been chilling, not doing much really, just relaxing and everything, just kind of take everything in.
We're actually in the quarter finals, top eight in the World Cup.
Get about it.
It's a special game, first of all, because I'm born in England, born in Leeds.
Could have played for England, and of course it's special that I'm playing there as well.
I've got so many friends on the team, I've got so many English friends as well.
It's a special game, definitely.
What's it like playing against people you train against every day?
Does anyone have an advantage?
No, I think it's...
I do it almost, not every game, but many games a year.
Against Arsenal, I'm playing against Martin, which is also weird because when we're in the national camp, we are with each other every single
day, so it's weird to play against him, City, Arsenal, because he's such a good friend.
And the same will be now when I play against the Jews, when I play against John, Nico, Mark, you know, it's weird because you know
them, and it's just funny, you just look at each other and you just smile, it's just fun.
But now on the pitch, it's 90 minutes of war against each other, you know.
Highlight of the World Cup?
Yeah.
There's been so many that it's been so difficult to kind of take.
Debut in the World Cup, going through, going through again.
Beating Brazil, it has to be beating Brazil because I never expected to progress from that round and to beat Brazil.
It's gone a long shot as well, I didn't expect that, so...
There's been so many people at that hotel there, just seeing me laying around here just screaming at you.
Serious?
Yeah.
Look now, one there again.
Look, she's filming me.
Look, she's waving.
Look at him.
Right by the beach with some people looking at us.
Come on, get on there.
Film them.
So it's good.
We're enjoying ourselves.
As a continent of 11.
Yeah, definitely.
Everything's exploded yet again.
I never thought in my life it could be this crazy, but the world and life proves me wrong every single time.
The memes?
Yeah, the memes out of this world.
It's so much funny memes.
Me sitting there eating, getting scared of myself.
It's so funny.
Me and Vinny singing.
Yeah, there's so many.
I go on my phone and I just keep getting new memes.
You know, it's too funny.
England tomorrow, quarter-final in the World Cup.
I expect England to win and us to go out.
Then we're gonna head straight to Norway, Oslo, greet the king.
It's been emotional, it's been nice, but now it's time to call it a day.
I think this will make Erling's YouTube channel even better.
An ancient shirt from the age of the Vikings.
Now a big question.
Who's gonna wear this?
I don't know.
Hilberto Mora?
We want you to wear it.
Yes?
Yes.
87, very nice.
Beautiful!
You got it, mate!
Where is the big f***ing guy?
Hello!
Oh!
Big white king!
What happened with his hair?
Where did the hair go?
I had to cut my hair so he could shine, or else we were two.
There is no place for two.
There is place only for one.
I had my time.
I step aside.
I sit, and now.
He's shining.
But look at this class.
This is where we need to learn.
Watch, first of all, on the right hand.
We start with Alan.
When you're a millionaire, you look like this.
But when you're a billionaire, you look like this.
This is my hair.
But you will arrive, trust me.
Hopefully one day.
We had the same agent.
I'm not worried.
I know your path.
You were coming there.
I was the same when I was 35.
You know, Rafaela told me, if Zlatan tells me one more time that he was better than me, or is better than me, he's going to come and
kick his ass.
He kicked my ass.
That's okay.
I need to trigger him, or else everybody says, you're the best, you're the best.
You need to put objective.
I'm better scoring goals, but he's a better football player.
What's it been like watching Erling at this World Cup seeing how he's grown throughout grown?
He's already grown.
How much do you want him to grow?
Hopefully he stops there.
He doesn't need to grow.
What I would say, he has done what he absolutely has done, always scoring goals.
If you want goals, we call it Haaland.
But I think now they get to see the character also, which everybody is excited, and especially here in America.
The like, when you have the, when you're a character, that's it.
And I made him make 20 million followers just by saying he don't need to cut his hair, so it became crazy.
You're even singing now.
What the f*** is that, my friend?
Can you sing also?
I didn't, I don't know how to sing.
That's a special talent we haven't seen from you.
Then you have your YouTube, you have your book now.
I saw, if you're from Scandinavia and you have personality, either they don't accept it or something is wrong.
So that's why we like personalities.
Without personalities, we just one of many.
We don't like to be one of many.
We want to be the number one.
That's the way we work.
And if you have personality, character, you're going to reach that level.
Now you understand why I like this guy, no?
If you have personality, it's like you go to McDonald's.
The guy who doesn't have personality will stay in the line outside.
The guy with the personality passed the line and he makes his order.
That's the way we work.
That's not normal for Scandinavia.
That's why we love him and they love God.
That's the way we are.
So I'm just happy somebody after me comes and he brings it to the next level.
It's the end of the world, Co. Can you just reflect for a second?
My friend, they just pay you to hold the camera or also to talk?
A bit of both.
So they pay one and they get two.
Exactly!
I'm paying, so it's a good deal.
Ah, this is your guy, not the Norwegian.
No, no, no, me, me, this is my YouTube.
Ah, this is your YouTube!
Ah, we're gonna get you more followers now, don't worry.
So we can talk a lot of s**t.
I saw some clip with the elevator, did you see that one?
Where they stretch your neck.
Like when he talks.
I don't know if you noticed, a lot of fans had the wig.
Yeah, yeah, I saw today.
But it was on competition today.
All over the place where we were.
But if you're playing with today, with social media, you would be fourth.
I'm not proactive.
To be honest, I started late also, and I was like, I don't like it because people have different life in the social media, and then in reality
is different.
I choose to irritate people.
And if I get a bad comment, I succeed.
Because they take it too serious with this social media.
You know the best was when he signed for United.
Oh yeah.
And he just put it himself.
No?
Before the announcement?
When Mino was alive, we were in Monaco one week and we waited, we waited and I was like, Mino, I cannot wait anymore.
No, no, no, you have to have patience because they're on the stock market, we cannot say nothing.
Yeah, I don't give a f***.
With one post, I destroyed the whole marketing plan.
You chose my next destination.
Next destination, yes.
Oh, I said in TV, you promised me one goal and the shirt, but the goal I didn't get.
By the way, I wrote Swedish on purpose wrong.
What do you think?
The Swedish.
King.
It's good.
You should have written from the best to the best.
That's the next step.
I'm too humble.
No, no, no.
I need to be more like Zlatan.
The Vikings.
It's a nice shirt, though.
Do you like it?
It's amazing.
Listen, everything you have done is amazing.
With the robe, with the shirt, with the number.
The picture of the team was crazy.
But honestly, it's been amazing.
Like, everything.
Because the US, it's different, you know?
It's different.
Everything you have done has been like...
And they push it in this country.
In other countries, it will be like, yeah, whatever.
Here, they're really pushing.
You can feel it as well.
Here, those things, they speak more about the fancy things than actually the tactic.
How will you play?
It's less important.
They don't care.
They just want...
Football's going to go big here now.
The show was gone.
It will change.
All right.
Let's see.
If US would have won, would be good.
Then it's like successful World Cup.
Yeah, yeah.
Instead now it became like, it didn't develop.
Okay, we are still where we were 20 years ago.
So they needed the win against Belgium, but but it was not easy.
I still think they did good for them to be.
Come on, they had momentum, but then the reality came in the picture.
You and the Mbappe inspire American kids, surely.
Yeah, I think so.
But I still think it's such a big country and but the best has been like the bigger names.
Oh, yeah, everybody is delivered.
That was important for America because that's they like stars.
The only thing they want to talk about is the stars.
Yeah, yeah.
So it was him, but was crazy.
Every game was like two goals, two goals, or even Messi.
You've been with man, the best.
That's good.
The best quiet guy, but very good.
Yeah, he's natural.
Everything is natural.
What do people buy you for in your career?
Like what was the biggest?
No, I went always for free, so I could earn a lot of money.
No, no, no.
We did some transfers to be honest.
We did some transfers.
Come on, Mario.
This is my Italian physio.
He remembers me.
How are you?
All good?
Good.
Are you his personal physio?
Yes.
He kidnapped me.
But today he had cramps.
No.
He had a dead leg.
Yeah, but he had cramps, it's your fault, you didn't treat him good.
You have to cut tall.
You have to treat the left leg.
What a guy, what a legend.
Guys, I'm officially out of the World Cup, but Zlatan made me get my mood back up.
The man, the myth, the legend, Zlatan.
What a guy.
Amazing
reception.
Norwegians, I think they are really happy for what we've done in the World Cup so far, so good.
Meeting the king, no?
Yeah, come on, let's have it!
Come on, let's have it!
I'm not going to do it, it's not going to work!
Toto Castle with the King!
I'm
sorry.
Thank you.
No!